<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Affirmation</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="FGirls">For girls</string>
    <string name="Girls">For girls</string>
    <string name="_10">These top 10 affirmations for women are aimed at increasing sexuality and accepting oneself. Some of them are based on the writings of Natalia Pravdina, who did a great job in studying this issue.</string>
    <string name="_1">" 1. I am happy that I was born a woman. I radiate inner light and positive energy."</string>
    <string name="_2">2. I love myself the way I am. I fully and unconditionally accept myself.</string>
    <string name="_3">3. I am unique, beautiful, young, energetic and sexy.</string>
    <string name="_4">4. I attract attention and attract the love of men.</string>
    <string name="_5">5. I am constantly cultivating myself and getting better every minute.</string>
    <string name="_6">6. I am wise, self-confident, and independent.</string>
    <string name="_7">7. I get everything I want. The universe loves me. I deserve happiness.</string>
    <string name="_8">8. I am responsible for my life, and I fully control it.</string>
    <string name="_9">9. I am a self-sufficient and harmonious person. I have money, health and inspiration to realize all our plans.</string>
    <string name="_10g">10. I have everything I need: finance, health, beauty, love.</string>
    <string name="eg">Speak these phrases regularly, and you will quickly notice positive changes.</string>
    <string name="Guy">For men</string>
    <string name="gi">Regular repetition of these settings will help a man to pump over any vital sphere.</string>
    <string name="g10">10. I am filled with energy every second, and become even better.</string>
    <string name="g9">9. I am successful and energetic, so I want everything I want.</string>
    <string name="g8">8. My body is powerful, strong, healthy and beautiful.</string>
    <string name="g7">7. The universe helps and patronizes me: every day I get many opportunities for self-expression, and the realization of my life goals.</string>
    <string name="g6">6. Nature has endowed me with sound health, keen mind and beauty.</string>
    <string name="g5">5. I am healthy, strong, independent, successful and happy.</string>
    <string name="g4">4. I am smart, handsome, successful and rich.</string>
    <string name="g3">3. I provide my family with everything that they need, and I live in full prosperity.</string>
    <string name="g2">2. Women like me: I attract their attention and love.</string>
    <string name="g1">1. I am successful and self-sufficient.</string>
    <string name="g">These powerful affirmations are aimed at success, attracting money, and increasing self-esteem in men.</string>
    <string name="dos">On affluence</string>
    <string name="proc">To prosperity</string>
    <string name="usp">For success</string>
    <string name="udac">For good luck</string>
    <string name="zdorov">For good health</string>
    <string name="lubov">For love</string>
    <string name="hudoy">Slimming</string>
    <string name="kd">On every day</string>
    <string name="fgg">For guys</string>
    <string name="d">To attract money and wealth</string>
    <string name="dd">These affirmations are aimed at attracting money, financial well-being and material independence.</string>
    <string name="d1">1. I deserve, and so I get everything I want.</string>
    <string name="d2">2. I attract money to me, they love me, and they easily come into my life.</string>
    <string name="d3">3. I can earn a lot more than required.</string>
    <string name="d4">4. I provide all the benefits of myself and people close to me.</string>
    <string name="d5">5. I am financially independent and control my income.</string>
    <string name="d6">6. I attract luck, money loves me. I am a creative person with great prospects.</string>
    <string name="d7">7. I do everything in time and perfectly organize the workflow.</string>
    <string name="d8">8. I am a great worker and get a generous reward for it.</string>
    <string name="d9">9. I am an excellent specialist in my field: I easily and happily do the work, and get a decent pay.</string>
    <string name="d10">10. My life is filled with an abundance of resources, opportunities and finances.</string>
    <string name="dv">Choose the most suitable setting for yourself, and pronounce it regularly.</string>
    <string name="bac">BB</string>
    <string name="ed">Affirmations for every day</string>
    <string name="edd">These settings you can use the sutra to make your day even better.</string>
    <string name="ed1">1. This is my best day.</string>
    <string name="ed2">2. I am full of life energy.</string>
    <string name="ed3">3. I am overwhelmed with joy and love for people, and they reciprocate me.</string>
    <string name="ed4">4. Today I am irresistible: I look great, radiate positive, full of strength for grandiose accomplishments.</string>
    <string name="ed5">5. This day is productive, and brings me real pleasure.</string>
    <string name="ed6">6. I enjoy every minute, because it is unique.</string>
    <string name="ed7">7. I radiate happiness, joy and success.</string>
    <string name="ed8">8. I am grateful for every day of my life, because it is beautiful.</string>
    <string name="ed9">9. My intentions are pure. I abandon negative and destructive thoughts.</string>
    <string name="ed10">10. Love lives in my heart, I forgive all insults and is set for success and prosperity.</string>
    <string name="edv">Take advantage of these powerful affirmations and make your life even better.</string>
    <string name="ml">To attract love</string>
    <string name="ll">We have collected the best positive attitudes, it is for these sources on the Internet the most positive feedback.</string>
    <string name="l1">1. I am filled with inner light and love.</string>
    <string name="l2">2. I sincerely love everyone around, and I reciprocate.</string>
    <string name="l3">3. I am happy (a) in personal relationships and satisfied in the intimate sphere.</string>
    <string name="l4">4. I have a great partner: he inspires, supports and understands me.</string>
    <string name="l5">5. I am happy (a) every day to love and be loved (oops). I feel the joy of knowing myself and my half.</string>
    <string name="l6">6. Love overwhelms me. I am open to new relationships and emotions.</string>
    <string name="l7">7. I inspire and admire my partner. I am happy to be with this person.</string>
    <string name="l8">8. I get pleasure from intimate relationships and communication with my soulmate. I deserve love, and radiate it with every cell of my body.</string>
    <string name="l9">9. I gladly surrender to my partner and receive reciprocity from him. We admire each other.</string>
    <string name="l10">10. I am immensely happy.</string>
    <string name="lv">These settings are suitable for both men and women. Regularly pronounce these affirmations, and soon you will notice positive changes in your personal life and intimate sphere.</string>
    <string name="u">To attract good luck</string>
    <string name="uu">To always bring you luck, use these affirmations.</string>
    <string name="u1">1. Luck always follows me.</string>
    <string name="u2">2. I am lucky in any undertaking. I am confident in the future.</string>
    <string name="u3">3. I\'m lucky, because the universe loves me.</string>
    <string name="u4">4. I get all the benefits that I need, as good luck accompanies me.</string>
    <string name="u5">5. I attract success and good luck is always on my side.</string>
    <string name="u6">6. I know exactly what to do to achieve success and prosperity in life.</string>
    <string name="u7">7. I fully accept and understand myself. This allows me to be always successful and lucky.</string>
    <string name="u8">8. I have been successful, and satisfied with it.</string>
    <string name="u9">9. I am sure that luck will always follow me.</string>
    <string name="u10">10. Success is my everyday state, which brings me joy.</string>
    <string name="uv">These affirmations to attract good luck are suitable for both men and women.</string>
    <string name="p">For effective weight loss</string>
    <string name="pp">To speed up the process of getting rid of extra pounds, use the following positive installation.</string>
    <string name="p1">1. I am beautiful: I have a slim body and a perfect figure.</string>
    <string name="p2">2. I lose weight quickly and easily, and I enjoy it.</string>
    <string name="p3">3. My kilograms melt before my eyes, like snow in the warm spring sun.</string>
    <string name="p4">4. I love and accept myself.</string>
    <string name="p5">5. I am slim, fit, pumped up. I feel comfortable in my weight.</string>
    <string name="p6">6. I easily lose weight, and am satisfied with my result.</string>
    <string name="p7">7. I am perfect, and my weight is normal.</string>
    <string name="p8">8. I eat little and feel full and satisfied.</string>
    <string name="p9">9. I train effectively. Sports bring me real pleasure and burn a lot of calories.</string>
    <string name="p10">10. I consistently lose weight. Every day my body looks better and better.</string>
    <string name="pv">Starting the process of losing weight, select the appropriate settings for yourself, and tune in to a positive result.</string>
    <string name="pr">To prosperity</string>
    <string name="prr">These affirmations can be used every day to improve overall quality of life.</string>
    <string name="pr1">1. I am a successful, happy and realized person.</string>
    <string name="us">To attract success</string>
    <string name="prV">Choose the most suitable setting for yourself, and pronounce it regularly.</string>
    <string name="pr10">10. I am calm, focused, deliberately make decisions and they are always right.</string>
    <string name="pr2">2. I just have enough. I control the situation, and in general my life. Easily and with pleasure I care about close people.</string>
    <string name="pr3">3. The universe loves me and provides a lot of opportunities every day.</string>
    <string name="pr4">4. I have everything under control: health, career, finances, personal life.</string>
    <string name="pr5">5. All my undertakings are successful, and dreams come true.</string>
    <string name="pr6">6. Everything I want is realized.</string>
    <string name="pr7">7. I can do everything. My heart is filled with joy and happiness.</string>
    <string name="pr8">8. I get everything I need and more. Every day is filled with joy and new impressions.</string>
    <string name="pr9">9. I always get lucky, God loves and cares for me.</string>
    <string name="uss">If you want to be successful and achieve better results, the following installations will help you.</string>
    <string name="us1">1. Today I have many opportunities to prove myself. Everything goes in the best way.</string>
    <string name="us2">2. I always get lucky. Success accompanies me in any endeavors.</string>
    <string name="us3">3. I get everything I want.</string>
    <string name="zv">In the area of ​​attracting health into her life, Louise Hay made a great contribution.</string>
    <string name="us4">4. I am successful, for God loves me.</string>
    <string name="us5">5. I am strong mentally and physically.</string>
    <string name="us6">6. Every breath fills me with confidence, and exhale carries away fears and doubts.</string>
    <string name="us7">7. In me inexhaustible energy is boiling. I can do anything.</string>
    <string name="us8">8. I attract only open and positive people to my life.</string>
    <string name="us9">9. I am happy that I can control my life myself, and I am confident in the future.</string>
    <string name="us10">10. I easily find a way out of any situation, think outside the box and creatively, generate the best solutions.</string>
    <string name="usv">Judging by the opinions of people who used affirmations for success, after 7 days, they experienced significant changes in their lives.</string>
    <string name="z">To attract health</string>
    <string name="zz">To preserve and strengthen your health, apply the following texts.</string>
    <string name="z1">1. I am strong, strong in spirit and resilient.</string>
    <string name="z2">2. My body is perfect.</string>
    <string name="z3">3. I am full of health, joy and energy.</string>
    <string name="z4">4. I take care of my body, and it makes me happy.</string>
    <string name="z5">5. My organs work as one balanced and tuned mechanism. They do an excellent job with their functions.</string>
    <string name="z6">6. I am young, strong, healthy, dexterous, fast, hardy. I have a healthy body and strong spirit.</string>
    <string name="z7">7. I feel great and enjoy every moment.</string>
    <string name="z8">8. I am grateful for my health and beauty.</string>
    <string name="z9">9. I am aware and feel my power.</string>
    <string name="z10">10. I enjoy life here and now, because I have everything I need.</string>
</resources>